Simon Game User Manual [This manual is also saved in the zip file]
By Jianeng Wang

Before the Game
1. Keep your hands DRY before start
2. Wipe the touchpad with a dry, clean tissue
3. Better put on a pair of sun glasses
4. Look CAREFULLY and Be PATIENT
5. Sometimes, the light will shine due to sensitivity of touchpad. Just try again.
6. Put a tape on the touchpad to make input more reliable
7. If you cannot debug, try: Run->Debug Configurations->Right click "GDB PEMicro Interface Debugging"->New->Debugger->Choose "OpenSDA Embedded Debug - USB Port" for Interface, "USB1 -OpenSDA(85447E45)" for Port->Choose "KL25Z128M4" for Select Device
Then Click on "Apply", and Debug

Color Meaning
Yellow-Get Ready
Red,Green,Blue shining-Indicate the random number has been generated, Game start
Purple, Yellow, Cyan shining- end of a sequence
White- Indicate Missing Color
Purple- Correct
Cyan- Wrong
Rainbow-Game Over

In game
1. the user should start to prepare with a YELLOW Light
2. Press the touchpad and You will see A flash of RED, GREEN, BLUE light
3. Get ready and you will see a sequence of light
4. A sequence of shining Purple, Yellow and Cyan will indicate the sequnce is over
5. A sequnce with color(s) missing, the position for a missing color would be indicated by white
6. A sequence of shining Purple, Yellow and Cyan will indicate the missing sequnce is over
7. Press the touchpad with the right order of missing color(s).Left-RED, Middle- Green, Right- Blue
8. YOU will see a color indicating the result
Purple- Congratulations, you will move on to the HELL mode, the sequence will be extended    ヽ(✿ﾟ▽ﾟ)ノ
Cyan- You lose. You would see a rainbow and then you will see the yellow light and try again.   Σ(っ °Д °;)っ

Have Fun
<(￣ㄧ￣ )

